Finding Aid for James K. Pollock Papers, 1920-1968
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Correspondence 1912-1968, 26 linear feet
  - 1926-1939 1936-1939
    - National Municipal League 1934-1938 (Box 5)
      [5-20]
    - National Municipal League, 1931-1932,1934 1938-1939 (Box 5)
      [5-21]
    - National Policy Committee 1937-1939 (Box 6)
      [6-1]
    - Nye, Gerald P. 1930-1939 (Box 6)
      [6-2]
    - O 1936-1939 (Box 6)
      [6-3]
    - Ogg, Frederic A. 1925-1939 (Box 6)
      [6-4]
    - Oratorical Association, University of Michigan 1934-1936 (Box 6)
      [6-5]
    - P 1936-1939 (Box 6)
      [6-6]
    - Personnel (Subcommittee on Personnel Standards of the Interstate Conference) 1937 (Box 6)
      [6-7a]
    - Personnel. Conference of Government Personnel in Michigan May 1936 (Box 6)
      [6-7b]
    - Political Science Department, University of Michigan 1936-1939 (Box 6)
      [6-7c]
    - Quadrangle Club 1932-1933 (Box 6)
      [6-7d]
    - Ra-Ri 1936-1939 (Box 6)
      [6-8]
    - Ro-Ry 1936-1939 (Box 6)
      [6-9]
    - Republican National Committee 1920-1938 (Box 6)
      [6-10]
    - Ruthven, Alexander G. 1932-1939 (Box 6)
      [6-11]
    - Sa-Ses 1936-1939 (Box 6)
      [6-12]
    - Sch 1936-1939 (Box 6)
      [6-13]
    - Se-Sh 1936-1939 (Box 6)
      [6-14]
    - Si-Sp 1936-1939 (Box 6)
      [6-15]
    - St-Sw 1936-1939 (Box 6)
      [6-16]
    - Schorer, Arno 1938-1939 (Box 6)
      [6-17]
    - Social Science Research Council 1926-1935 (Box 6)
      [6-18]
    - Social Science Research: "Report of the Sub-Committee on Local Research to the Committee on Social Science Research, University of Michigan," 1934 (Box 6)
      [6-19]
    - T 1936-1939 (Box 6)
      [6-20]
    - U 1936-1939 (Box 7)
      [7-1]
    - University Lectures: Committee on University Lectures 1937-1939 (Box 7)
      [7-3a]
    - University of Michigan, Bureau of Alumni Relations 1932-1936 (Box 7)
      [7-3b]
    - University of Michigan, Institute of Public and Social Administration 1936 (Box 7)
      [7-3c]
    - University of Michigan, Student-Faculty Sub-committee on Student Attitudes 1934 (Box 7)
      [7-3d]
    - Upson, Lent D. 1935-1939 (Box 7)
      [7-2]
    - V 1932, 1936-1939 (Box 7)
      [7-4]
    - Van Nostrand (D. Van Nostrand Co.,Inc.) 1938-1939 (Box 7)
      [7-5]
    - Van Nostrand (D. Van Nostrand Co.,Inc.) 1933-1937 (Box 7)
      [7-6]
    - Wa-We 1936-1939 (Box 7)
      [7-7]
    - Wh-Wz 1936-1939 (Box 7)
      [7-8]
    - Y-Z 1936-1939 (Box 7)
      [7-9]
  - 1938-1945 1940-1945
    - A 1940-1945 (Box 7)
      [7-12]
    - American Political Science Association 1939-1945 (Box 7)
      [7-13]
    - Ann Arbor Citizens Council 1941-1942 (Box 7)
      [7-14]
    - Ba-Be 1938-1945 (Box 7)
      [7-15]
    - Bi-Bo 1940-1945 (Box 7)
      [7-16]
    - Br 1940-1945 (Box 7)
      [7-17]
    - Bu-By (Box 7)
      [7-18]
    - Brownrigg, William 1940-1944 (Box 8)
      [8-1]
    - Bureau of Appointments, University of Michigan (recommendations for the) 1940-1945 (Box 8)
      [8-2]
    - Ca-Ch 1940-1945 (Box 8)
      [8-3]
    - Ci-Com 1940-1945 (Box 8)
      [8-4]
    - Con-Cz 1940-1945 (Box 8)
      [8-5]
    - Committee on University Lectures 1940-1945 (Box 8)
      [8-6b]
    - Crofts, F.S. 1939-1944 (Box 8)
      [8-6a]
    - Current History article on Germany, 1942 (Box 8)
      [8-6c]
    - Da-De 1940-1945 (Box 8)
      [8-7]
    - Di-Du 1939-1945 (Box 8)
      [8-8]
    - E 1940-1945 (Box 8)
      [8-9]
    - Economic Status of Faculty 1945 (Box 8)
      [8-10a]
    - Extension Service, University of Michigan 1939-1945 (Box 8)
      [8-10b]
    - Fa-Fl 1940-1945 (Box 8)
      [8-11]
    - Fo-Fu 1940-1945 (Box 8)
      [8-12]
    - Ferguson, Homer 1942-1945 (Box 8)
      [8-13]
    - Fortune Magazine (Box 8)
      [8-14]
    - Ga-Gi 1940-1945 (Box 8)
      [8-15]
    - Gl-Gu 1940-1945 (Box 8)
      [8-16]
    - Ha 1940-1945 (Box 8)
      [8-17]
    - He 1940-1945 (Box 8)
      [8-18]
    - Hi 1940-1945 (Box 8)
      [8-19]
    - Ho-Hy 1940-1945 (Box 9)
      [9-1]
    - Hayden, Joseph R. 1940-1944 (Box 9)
      [9-2a]
    - Harper and Brothers 1939-1943 (Box 9)
      [9-2b]
    - I 1940-1945 (Box 9)
      [9-2c]
    - J 1940-1945 (Box 9)
      [9-3]
    - Judd, Mrs. Siegel W. (Dorothy) 1939-1945 (Box 9)
      [9-4]
    - Judge Advocate General's School, University of Michigan 1943-1945 (Box 9)
      [9-5]
    - Ka-Kem 1940-1945 (Box 9)
      [9-6]
    - Ken-Ki 1940-1945 (Box 9)
      [9-7]
    - Kn-Ku 1940-1945 (Box 9)
      [9-8]
    - Kennedy, James A. 1939-1943 (Box 9)
      [9-9]
    - Knopf. Alfred A. Knopf Co. 1941-1944 (Box 9)
      [9-10a]
    - Kraus, Dean Edward H. 1940-1944 (Box 9)
      [9-10b]
    - La-Led 1940-1945 (Box 9)
      [9-11]
    - Lee-Lov 1940-1945 (Box 9)
      [9-12]
    - Lovett, William P. 1941-1945 (Box 9)
      [9-13]
    - Lovett, William P. 1940 (Box 9)
      [9-14a]
    - Lo-Ly 1940-1945 (Box 9)
      [9-14b]
    - Litchfield, Edward H. 1940-1945 (Box 9)
      [9-15]
    - Me-Mac 1940-1945 (Box 9)
      [9-16]
    - Ma 1940-1945 (Box 9)
      [9-17]
    - Me-Mid 1940-1945 (Box 9)
      [9-18]
    - Mil-Mit 1938-1939 (Box 9)
      [9-19]
    - Mo-My 1940-1945 (Box 9)
      [9-20]
    - Michigan Merit System Association 1940-1941, 1944 (Box 9)
      [9-21]
    - Na-Ne 1940-1945 (Box 10)
      [10-1]
    - Ni-Ny 1940-1945 (Box 10)
      [10-2]
    - National Municipal League 1940-1945 (Box 10)
      [10-3a]
    - Neff, Mortimer A. 1941-1943 (Box 10)
      [10-3b]
    - National Civil Service Reform League 1940-1945 (Box 10)
      [10-4]
    - O 1940-1945 (Box 10)
      [10-5a]
    - Ogg, Frederick A. 1940-1945 (Box 10)
      [10-5b]
    - Pa-Pe 1940-1945 (Box 10)
      [10-6]
    - Pf-Pu 1940-1945 (Box 10)
      [10-7]
    - Pratt, F.D. (Time, Inc.) 1940-1941 (Box 10)
      [10-8a]
    - Q 1935, 1940 (Box 10)
      [10-8b]
    - Ra-Ri 1940-1945 (Box 10)
      [10-9]
    - Ro-Ru 1940-1945 (Box 10)
      [10-10]
    - Sa-Schaa 1940-1945 (Box 10)
      [10-11]
    - Schat-Se 1940-1945 (Box 10)
      [10-12]
    - Sh-Sp 1940-1945 (Box 10)
      [10-13]
    - St-Sw 1940-1945 (Box 10)
      [10-14]
    - Ta-Th 1940-1945 (Box 10)
      [10-15]
    - Ti-Ty 1940-1945 (Box 10)
      [10-16]
    - U 1939-1945 (Box 10)
      [10-17]
    - V 1940-1945 (Box 10)
      [10-18]
    - Van Nostrand. D. Van Nostrand Co., Inc. 1939-1944 (Box 10)
      [10-19]
    - Wa 1940-1945 (Box 11)
      [11-1]
    - We-Wh 1940-1945 (Box 11)
      [11-2]
    - Wi-Wy (Box 11)
      [11-3]
    - Y-Z 1940-1945 (Box 11)
      [11-4a]
    - Yoakum, Dean C.S. 1940-1945 (Box 11)
      [11-4b]
  - 1945-1961 1946-1960
    - A-Allen 1946-1960 (Box 11)
      [11-5]
    - Alli-Am 1946-1961 (Box 11)
      [11-6]
    - An-Ay 1946-1959 (Box 11)
      [11-8]
    - Africa, Bernabe 1951-1958 (Box 11)
      [11-9]
    - American Association of University Women 1949-1956 (Box 11)
      [11-7a]
    - American Committee for Study of War Documents 1955-1957 (Box 11)
      [11-7b]
    - American Political Science Association 1951-1957 (Box 11)
      [11-11]
    - American Political Science Association, Census Advisory Committee 1952-1953 (Box 11)
      [11-10]
    - American Political Science Association, Cooperative Research Project on Convention Delegates 1952-1954 (Box 11)
      [11-12]
    - American Society for Public Administration 1946-1958 (Box 11)
      [11-14]
    - Ba 1946-1961 (Box 11)
      [11-15]
    - Be 1946-1960 (Box 11)
      [11-16]
    - Bh-Bo 1946-1960 (Box 11)
      [11-17]
    - Br 1946-1960 (Box 11)
      [11-18]
    - Brookings Institution study on presidential nominating procedures 1953-1957 (Box 11)
      [11-13]
    - Bu-By 1946-1960 (Box 12)
      [12-1]
    - Barclay, Thomas 1947-1959 (Box 12)
      [12-2]
    - Ca-Ce 1946-1960 (Box 12)
      [12-3]
    - Ch-Cl 1946-1960 (Box 12)
      [12-4]
    - Co 1946-1960 (Box 12)
      [12-5]
    - Cr-Cy 1946-1960 (Box 12)
      [12-6]
    - Chairmanship of U-M Dept. of Political Science 1947-1958 (scattered dates) (Box 12)
      [12-7]
    - Citizens Committee for the Hoover Report 1948-1954, 1958 (Box 12)
      [12-8]
    - Da 1946-1960 (Box 12)
      [12-9]
    - De-Di 1945-1960 (Box 12)
      [12-10]
    - Dj-Dy 1946-1960 (Box 12)
      [12-11]
    - Ea-Ed (Box 12)
      [12-12]
    - Ef-Ei 1946-1960 (Box 12)
      [12-13]
    - El 1946-1960 (Box 12)
      [12-14]
    - Em-Ew 1946-1960 (Box 12)
      [12-15]
    - Fa-Fe 1946-1960 (Box 12)
      [12-16]
    - Fi-Fo 1946-1960 (Box 12)
      [12-17]
    - Fr-Fy 1946-1960 (Box 12)
      [12-18]
    - Foreign Policy Association 1946-1952 (Box 12)
      [12-19]
    - Ga-Ge 1946-1960 (Box 13)
      [13-1]
    - Gi-Go 1946-1960 (Box 13)
      [13-2]
    - Gr 1946-1960 (Box 13)
      [13-3]
    - Gu-Gy 1945-1960 (Box 13)
      [13-4]
    - Ha-Han 1946-1960 (Box 13)
      [13-5]
    - Har 1946-1960 (Box 13)
      [13-6]
    - Has-Haz 1946-1960 (Box 13)
      [13-7]
    - He 1946-1960 (Box 13)
      [13-8]
    - Hi 1946-1960 (Box 13)
      [13-9]
    - Ho 1945-1960 (Box 13)
      [13-10]
    - Hs-Hy 1946-1960 (Box 13)
      [13-11]
    - Heuss, Theodor (re visit of Heuss in June 1958 to the United States and the University of Michigan) 1958 (Box 13)
      [13-12]
    - I 1946-1960 (Box 13)
      [13-13]
    - Ja-Je 1946-1960 (Box 13)
      [13-14]
    - Jo-Ju 1946-1960 (Box 13)
      [13-15]
    - Ka-Kem 1946-1960 (Box 13)
      [13-16]
    - Ken-Key 1946-1960 (Box 13)
      [13-17]
    - Kh-Kn 1946-1960 (Box 13)
      [13-18]
    - Ko-Ku 1946-1960 (Box 13)
      [13-19]
    - La 1946-1960 (Box 13)
      [13-20]
    - Le 1946-1960 (Box 13)
      [13-21]
    - Li-Lin 1946-1960 (Box 14)
      [14-1]
    - Lip-Lof 1946-1960 (Box 14)
      [14-2]
    - Loe-Ly 1946-1960 (Box 14)
      [14-3a]
    - Litchfield, Edward H
      - 1946-1949 (Box 14)
        [14-3b]
      - 1950-1951 (Box 14)
        [14-3c]
      - 1952-1954 (Box 14)
        [14-3d]
    - Mac-Mars 1945-1960 (Box 14)
      [14-4]
    - Mart-May 1946-1960 (Box 14)
      [14-5]
    - Mc 1946-1960 (Box 14)
      [14-6]
    - Me 1946-1960 (Box 14)
      [14-7]
    - Mi 1946-1960 (Box 14)
      [14-8]
    - Mo 1946-1960 (Box 14)
      [14-9]
    - Mu-My 1946-1960 (Box 14)
      [14-10a]
    - Mettger, H. Philip 1946, 1949-1953 (Box 14)
      [14-10b]
    - Mettger, H. Philip 1953-1959 (Box 14)
      [14-11a]
    - Meynaud, Jean 1951-1953 (Box 14)
      [14-11b]
    - Moody, Blair 1947-1954 (Box 14)
      [14-11c]
    - Na-Neal 1946-1960 (Box 14)
      [14-12]
    - Nee-New 1946-1960 (Box 14)
      [14-13]
    - Ni-Nu 1946-1960 (Box 14)
      [14-14]
    - O 1946-1960 (Box 14)
      [14-15a]
    - Ogg, Frederick A. 1940, 1945-1951 (Box 14)
      [14-15b]
    - Pa 1946-1960 (Box 14)
      [14-16]
    - Pe 1946-1960 (Box 14)
      [14-17]
    - Pf-Pl 1946-1960 (Box 14)
      [14-18]
    - Po 1946-1960 (Box 14)
      [14-19]
    - Pr-Q 1946-1960 (Box 14)
      [14-20]
    - Ra-Re 1946-1961 (Box 15)
      [15-1]
    - Ri-Rog 1946-1960 (Box 15)
      [15-2]
    - Rok-Roy 1946-1960 (Box 15)
      [15-3]
    - Ru-Ry 1946-1960 (Box 15)
      [15-4a]
    - Ruthven, Alexander G. 1940-1957 (Box 15)
      [15-4b]
    - Rinehart and Company 1947-1952 (Box 15)
      [15-5]
    - Rome Congress, International Political Science Association 1958 (Box 15)
      [15-6]
    - Sa 1946-1960 (Box 15)
      [15-7]
    - Sc-Sch 1945-1960 (Box 15)
      [15-8]
    - Sco-Se 1946-1960 (Box 15)
      [15-9]
    - Sh 1946-1960 (Box 15)
      [15-10]
    - Si 1946-1960 (Box 15)
      [15-11]
    - Sk-Sm 1945-1960 (Box 15)
      [15-12]
    - Sn-So 1946-1960 (Box 15)
      [15-13]
    - Social Science Division of the College of LS&A, U-M 1939-1951 (Box 15)
      [15-14]
    - Sp-Sr 1945-1960 (Box 15)
      [15-15]
    - Sta 1946-1960 (Box 15)
      [15-16]
    - Ste-Stg 1946-1960 (Box 15)
      [15-17]
    - Sto-Stu 1946-1960 (Box 15)
      [15-18]
    - Su-Sz 1946-1960 (Box 15)
      [15-19]
    - Ta-Th 1946-1960 (Box 15)
      [15-20]
    - Ti-Ty 1946-1960 (Box 15)
      [15-21]
    - U 1946-1960 (Box 16)
      [16-1]
    - Va-Van 1946-1960 (Box 16)
      [16-2]
    - Vau-Vo 1946-1960 (Box 16)
      [16-3]
    - Wa-Wan 1946-1960 (Box 16)
      [16-4]
    - War-Wat 1945-1960 (Box 16)
      [16-5]
    - We 1946-1960 (Box 16)
      [16-6]
    - Wh-Wic 1946-1960 (Box 16)
      [16-7]
    - Wil-Wit 1946-1960 (Box 16)
      [16-8]
    - Wo-Woo 1945-1960 (Box 16)
      [16-9]
    - Wor-Wy 1946-1960 (Box 16)
      [16-10]
    - Y-Z 1946-1960 (Box 16)
      [16-11]
  - 1946-1966 1946-1965
    - A-Al 1949-1965 (Box 20)
      [20-18]
    - Am-Au 1959-1965 (Box 20)
      [20-19]
    - Advisory Committee on University Professorships 1965 (Box 20)
      [20-20a]
    - Alumni Association, Class Officers' Council 1955-1965 (Box 20)
      [20-20b]
    - American Academy of Political and Social Science 1946-1964 (Box 20)
      [20-21a]
    - American Society for Public Administration 1962, 1965 (Box 20)
      [20-21b]
    - American Enterprise Institute 1960-1965 (Box 21)
      [21-1]
    - American Political Science Association 1962-1965 (Box 21)
      [21-2a]
    - Atlantic Council of the United States 1964-1966 (Box 21)
      [21-2b]
    - Ba 1959-1965 (Box 21)
      [21-3]
    - Be-Bi 1947-1965 (Box 21)
      [21-4]
    - Bl-Bo 1949-1965 (Box 21)
      [21-5]
    - Bra-Bro 1954-1965 (Box 21)
      [21-6]
    - Bru-Bu 1952-1965 (Box 21)
      [21-7]
    - Brownell, Edmund B. 1949-1964 (Box 21)
      [21-8]
    - Brownell, Roy E. 1947-1965 (Box 21)
      [21-9]
    - Brownrigg, William 1946-1961 (Box 21)
      [21-10]
    - Ca 1947-1965 (Box 21)
      [21-11]
    - Ce-Ci 1960-1965 (Box 21)
      [21-12a]
    - Citizens Research Council of Michigan 1962-1966 (Box 21)
      [21-12b]
    - Citizens for Michigan 1959-1964 (Box 21)
      [21-13]
    - Civil Service
      - Michigan Civil Service Commission 1948-1965 (Box 21)
        [21-14]
      - Michigan State Employees Association 1954 (Box 21)
        [21-15a]
      - Michigan Civil Service Commission, Political Activity Advisory Committee 1961 (Box 21)
        [21-15b]
    - Class of 1920. Re reunions of the Class of 1920 of the U-M 1959-1960, 1964-1965 (Box 21)
      [21-16]
    - Clay, Lucius D. 1946-1965 (Box 21)
      [21-17]
    - Cl-Co 1960-1965 (Box 21)
      [21-18]
    - Coates, Charles B. 1952-1963 (Box 21)
      [21-19]
    - Cole, R. Taylor 1946-1965 (Box 21)
      [21-20]
    - Commission. Advisory Commission on Intergovernmental Relations 1962-1965 (Box 22)
      [22-1]
    - Commission. Governor's Special Commission on Legislative Compensation 1965 (Box 22)
      [22-2]
    - Committee. Census Advisory Committee on State and Local Government 1959-1963, 2 folders (Box 22)
      [21-4; 21-5]
    - Committee. Cook Lecture Committee, University of Michigan Law School 1958-1964 (Box 22)
      [22-5]
    - Constitution. Michigan Constitutional Convention 1961-1965, 2 folders (Box 22)
      [22-6; 22-7]
    - Cr-Cu 1961-1965 (Box 22)
      [22-8]
    - Crow, Allen B. 1946-1961 (Box 22)
      [22-9]
    - Da-De 1949-1965 (Box 22)
      [22-10]
    - Detroit Committee on Foreign Relations 1960-1965 (Box 22)
      [22-11]
    - Detroit Economic Club (Box 22)
      [22-17b]
    - DeWald, Frank K. 1960-1965 (Box 22)
      [22-12]
    - Di-Dj 1959-1964 (Box 22)
    - Do-Du 1952-1965 (Box 22)
    - Doctoral examinations and committees 1940-1967, 2 folders (Box 22)
      [22-15; 22-16]
    - Dryden Press 1952-1958 (Box 22)
      [22-17a]
    - Economic. Committee on the Economic Status of the Faculty, Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs 1944-1963, 3 folders (Box 22)
      [22-18; 22-19; 22-20]
    - E 1948-1965 (Box 23)
      [23-1]
    - Fa-Fl 1946-1965 (Box 23)
      [23-2]
    - Fo-Fu 1946-1965 (Box 23)
      [23-3]
    - Faculty Club (proposed University of Michigan Faculty Club) 1956-1965, 5 folders (Box 23)
      [23-4 to 23-8]
    - Ford Foundation 1962-1963 (Box 23)
      [23-9]
    - Foreign Leader Program (U.S. State Dept.), Indian Election Commissioner 1964 (Box 23)
      [23-10a]
    - Foundation for Foreign Affairs, Inc. 1965 (Box 23)
      [23-10b]
    - Freedoms Foundation, Valley Forge 1961-1964 (Box 23)
      [23-11]
    - Friedensburg, Ferdinand 1956-1965 (Box 23)
      [23-12]
    - Ga-Gi 1961-1965 (Box 23)
      [23-13]
    - Gl-Go 1949-1965 (Box 23)
      [23-14]
    - Gr-Gu 1952-1965 (Box 23)
      [23-15]
    - German Decoration material 1956 (Box 23)
      [23-16]
    - Ha-Han 1945-1965 (Box 23)
      [23-17]
    - Har-Haz 1951-1965 (Box 23)
      [23-18]
    - He 1949-1965 (Box 23)
      [23-19]
    - Hi-Hof 1948-1965 (Box 24)
      [24-1]
    - Hol-How 1947-1965 (Box 24)
      [24-2]
    - Hu-Hy 1950-1965 (Box 24)
      [24-3]
    - Huvanandana, Malai 1947-1964 (Box 24)
      [24-4a]
    - Hurtig, Serge (International Political Science Association) 1961-1965 (Box 24)
      [24-4b]
    - I 1958-1964 (Box 24)
      [24-5]
    - Interior Department (U.S.) 1953 (Box 24)
      [24-6]
    - Intercultural Relations, University of Michigan Committee on 1950-1960 (Box 24)
      [24-7]
    - J 1949-1965 (Box 24)
      [24-8]
    - Judd, Dorothy 1946-1965 (Box 24)
      [24-9]
    - Ka 1952-1965 (Box 24)
      [24-10]
    - Ke 1947-1965 (Box 24)
      [24-11]
    - Ki-Ko 1950-1965 (Box 24)
      [24-12]
    - Kr-Ku 1947-1965 (Box 24)
      [24-13]
    - Kern, Paul J. 1945-1965 (Box 24)
      [24-14]
    - Kirkpatrick, Evron M. 1954-1965 (Box 24)
      [24-15]
    - La 1954-1965 (Box 24)
      [24-16]
    - Le 1955-1965 (Box 24)
      [24-17]
    - Li 1947-1968 (Box 24)
      [24-18]
    - Ll-Ly 1949-1965 (Box 24)
      [24-19]
    - Lane, John C. (Box 24)
      [24-20]
    - Laves, Walter H.C. 1950-1962 (Box 25)
      [25-1]
    - Litchfield, Edward H. 1955-1965 (Box 25)
      [25-3]
    - Litchfield, Edward H. 1966-1968 (Box 25)
      [25-2]
    - Lieber. Franz Lieber Foundation 1955 (Box 25)
      [25-4]
    - Mac-Mah 1946-1967 (Box 25)
      [25-5]
    - Mai-May 1945-1968 (Box 25)
      [25-6]
    - Mc 1948-1965 (Box 25)
      [25-7]
    - Me 1959-1965 (Box 25)
      [25-8]
    - Meader, George 1946-1964 (Box 25)
      [25-9]
    - Menzel, Walter 1946-1960 (Box 25)
      [25-10a]
    - Mettger, H. Philip 1959-1965 (Box 25)
      [25-10b]
    - Mi 1955-1965 (Box 25)
      [25-11]
    - Midwest Political Science Association 1948-1965 (Box 25)
      [25-12]
    - Mo 1950-1965 (Box 25)
      [25-13]
    - Mu-My 1958-1965 (Box 25)
      [25-14]
    - National Civil Service 1949-1964 (Box 25)
      [25-15]
    - National Civil Service League, Committee on Employee Organization 1959-1960 (Box 25)
      [25-16]
    - National Municipal League
      - 1946-1963 (Box 25)
        [25-18]
      - 1963-1965, 2 folders (Box 25)
        [25-17; 25-19]
    - N 1950-1965 (Box 26)
      [26-1]
    - O 1952-1965 (Box 26)
      [26-2]
    - Pa-Pe 1947-1965 (Box 26)
      [26-3]
    - Pf-Pol 1947-1965 (Box 26)
      [26-4]
    - Pos-Pu 1954-1965 (Box 26)
      [26-5]
    - Pollock, James K
      - Distinguished Faculty Award 1959 (Box 26)
        [26-6a]
      - Faculty Research Projects 157 and 152 (Box 26)
        [26-6b]
      - Faculty Research Project 345 (accounts) (Box 26)
        [26-6c]
      - Personal file
        - 1927-1949 (Box 26)
          [26-7]
        - 1950-1961 (Box 26)
          [26-8]
        - 1960-1965 (Box 26)
          [26-9]
        - 1934-1960 (Box 26)
          [26-10a]
      - James K. Pollock work with the war dept. during World War II (Box 26)
        [26-10b]
      - James K. Pollock correspondence with students and others during World War II 1942-1945 (Box 26)
        [26-10c]
    - Q 1961-1962 (Box 26)
      [26-11]
    - Ra 1953-1965 (Box 26)
      [26-12]
    - Re-Ri 1949-1965 (Box 26)
      [26-13]
    - Rob 1949-1965 (Box 26)
      [26-14]
    - Roc-Ru 1946-1965 (Box 26)
      [26-15]
    - Reorganization of State Government, Advisory Committee on
      - 1958-1962 (Box 26)
        [26-16]
      - 1958, 1961 (Box 26)
        [26-17]
    - Republican Advisory Committee of Michigan 1960-1964 (Box 26)
      [26-18]
    - Romney, George 1962-1965 (Box 26)
      [26-19a]
    - Rumanian Trip 1958 (Box 26)
      [26-19b]
    - Sa 1959-1965 (Box 26)
      [26-20]
    - Scammon, Richard 1946-1965 (Box 26)
      [26-21]
    - Schaaf, C. Hart 1947-1965 (Box 27)
      [27-1]
    - Sch 1953-1965 (Box 27)
      [27-2]
    - Sco-Sey 1960-1965 (Box 27)
      [27-3]
    - Sh 1947-1965 (Box 27)
      [27-4]
    - Si-Sm 1946-1966 (Box 27)
      [27-5]
    - Sn-Sp 1959-1965 (Box 27)
      [27-6]
    - Staar, Richard F. 1952-1965 (Box 27)
      [27-7]
    - St 1957-1965 (Box 27)
      [27-8]
    - Su-Sz 1951-1965 (Box 27)
      [27-9]
    - Sesquicentennial Committee of the University of Michigan
      - 1967 (Box 27)
        [27-10]
      - 1964-1967, 2 folders (Box 27)
        [27-11; 27-12]
    - Ta-Th 1950-1965 (Box 27)
      [27-13]
    - Ti-Tu 1946-1965 (Box 27)
      [27-14]
    - U 1948-1965 (Box 27)
      [27-15]
    - V 1949-1965 (Box 27)
      [27-16]
    - Vandenberg (lectureship and proposed foreign policy center)
      - 1951-1968 (Box 27)
        [27-17]
      - 1951-1953, 2 folders (Box 27)
        [27-18; 27-19]
    - Vandenberg, Arthur H. 1946-1961 (Box 27)
      [27-20]
    - Van Nostrand and Co. 1946-1950 (Box 27)
      [27-20b]
    - Van Nostrand and Co. 1951-1963 (Box 27)
      [27-21]
    - Wa-Wal 1946-1965 (Box 28)
      [28-1]
    - Wan-Wat 1947-1965 (Box 28)
      [28-2]
    - We 1945-1965 (Box 28)
      [28-3]
    - Wh 1948-1965 (Box 28)
      [28-4]
    - Wi 1947-1965 (Box 28)
      [28-5]
    - Wo-Wu 1954-1965 (Box 28)
      [28-6]
    - Wilton Park (England) 1962-1966 (Box 28)
      [28-7a]
    - Wittwer, Konrad 1948-1965 (Box 28)
      [28-7b]
    - Y-Z 1961-1965 (Box 28)
      [28-7c]
  - 1946-1968 1966-1968
    - A-Amb 1962-1968 (Box 28)
      [28-8]
    - Ame-Az 1961-1968 (Box 28)
      [28-9]
    - American Political Science Association 1965-1967 (Box 28)
      [28-10]
    - Ba 1966-1968 (Box 28)
      [28-11]
    - Be-Bl 1966-1968 (Box 28)
      [28-12]
    - Bo-Br 1963-1968 (Box 28)
      [28-13]
    - Bu 1960-1968 (Box 28)
      [28-14]
    - Ca-Col 1966-1968 (Box 28)
      [28-15]
    - Com 1966-1968 (Box 28)
      [28-16]
    - Con-Cu 1966-1968 (Box 28)
      [28-17]
    - Committee on Distinguished University Professorships of the University of Michigan 1966-1967 (Box 28)
      [28-18]
    - D 1946-1968 (Box 28)
      [28-19]
    - Detroit Committee on Foreign Relations
      - 1966-1969 (Box 28)
        [28-20]
      - 1966-1968 (Box 28)
        [28-21]
    - E 1963-1968 (Box 29)
      [29-1]
    - F 1966-1968 (Box 29)
      [29-2]
    - Faculty Club of the U-M 1966-1968 (Box 29)
      [29-3]
    - G 1965-1968 (Box 29)
      [29-4]
    - Ha 1960-1968 (Box 29)
      [29-5]
    - He-Hy 1947-1968 (Box 29)
      [29-6]
    - I 1966-1968 (Box 29)
      [29-7a]
    - J 1966-1968 (Box 29)
      [29-7b]
    - Ka-Ke 1966-1968 (Box 29)
      [29-8]
    - Ki-Ky 1966-1968 (Box 29)
      [29-9]
    - L 1966-1968 (Box 29)
      [29-10]
    - Littell, Franklin 1966-1968 (Box 29)
      [29-11]
    - Ma-Me 1966-1968 (Box 29)
      [29-12]
    - Mi-My 1966-1968 (Box 29)
      [29-13]
    - N 1966-1968 (Box 29)
      [29-14]
    - O 1966-1968 (Box 29)
      [29-15]
    - Pollock, James K
      - Personal file 1966-1968 (Box 29)
        [29-16]
      - Personal file, biographical materials 1966-1968 (Box 29)
        [29-17]
      - Personal file, honorary degrees 1966-1968 (Box 29)
        [29-18a]
      - Central Porcupine Mines investments (Box 29)
        [29-18b]
      - Introductory letters and addresses of Europeans 1927-1929 (Box 29)
        [29-18c]
      - Introductory letters and addresses of Germans 1928-1932 (Box 29)
        [29-18d]
    - P 1966-1968 (Box 29)
      [29-19a]
    - Q 1966-1968 (Box 29)
      [29-19b]
    - R 1966-1968 (Box 29)
      [29-20]
    - Sa-Sc 1966-1968 (Box 29)